<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<title>Blog | MOIA</title>
		<link>https://www.moia.io/en/blog</link>
		<description>The MOIA blog you will learn everything that moves the MOIA community and get exciting insights into the world of MOIA.</description>
		<generator>website-stalker https://github.com/EdJoPaTo/website-stalker</generator>
		<item>
			<title>Autonomous ridepooling in Hamburg: MOIA starts tests with users</title>
			<link>https://www.moia.io/en/blog/autonomous-ridepooling-in-hamburg-moia-starts-tests-with-users</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<span>
				06.12.2024
			</span>
			Autonomous ridepooling in Hamburg can now be experienced. This was kicked off by an appointment with Dr. Anjes Tjarks, Hamburg's Senator for Transport and Mobility Transition, who joined media representatives on a test drive with the ID. Buzz AD to get an impression of the current developments.
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Autonomous Driving Level 4: A Glimpse into the Future of Public Transportation</title>
			<link>https://www.moia.io/en/blog/autonomous-driving-level-4</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<span>
				22.10.2024
			</span>
			Autonomous driving at Level 4 – a term that is increasingly becoming common even outside the mobility industry and raising high expectations. But what exactly does this classification entail, and what prerequisites must be met to truly achieve Level 4 in public transportation?
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Autonomous Ridepooling: What is it?</title>
			<link>https://www.moia.io/en/blog/autonomous-ridepooling</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<span>
				08.10.2024
			</span>
			In this article, we answer the most important questions surrounding the topic of autonomous ridepooling. It's about the opportunities to respond sustainably to societal changes through this forward-thinking mobility solution. We explain the advantages of autonomous ridepooling and the conditions under which such a service can establish itself.
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>AI takes over Safety Tasks from Driving Personnel in Autonomous Operations</title>
			<link>https://www.moia.io/en/blog/interior-analysis</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<span>
				10.09.2024
			</span>
			In collaboration with emotion3D, MOIA has developed an AI solution for interior analysis in the self-driving, fully electric ID. Buzz AD from Volkswagen. The software automates safety tasks previously performed by the driving personnel, such as checking whether passengers have properly fastened their seat belts.
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>An Interview with MOIA-Safety Driver Nicholas</title>
			<link>https://www.moia.io/en/blog/interview-safety-driver</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<span>
				16.07.2024
			</span>
			We at MOIA want to bring autonomous shuttles to the streets of Hamburg for public use. Currently, we are in the test phase. For testing purposes one or two safety drivers are in the vehicle. One of them is Nicholas, who tells us in an interview more about his job as a safety driver.
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Accessibility Hamburg: MOIA&apos;s barrier-free service</title>
			<link>https://www.moia.io/en/blog/accessibility-hamburg</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<span>
				06.05.2024
			</span>
			At the beginning of 2023, we added 15 accessible vehicles to our ridepooling fleet. And the current figures show: The demand for our service among wheelchair users and people with disabilities is enormous.
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Autonomy recap: strong partnerships for the mobility transition</title>
			<link>https://www.moia.io/en/blog/Autonomy-in-Paris</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<span>
				25.03.2024
			</span>
			For the first time, MOIA was represented at the international trade fair for sustainable mobility solutions, the Autonomy Mobility World Expo in Paris. The international trade fair for sustainable mobility solutions took place on 20 and 21 March in Paris. It is directed at companies, start-ups, political decision-makers, institutions and NGOs.
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ridepooling in Europe: What services are offered where?</title>
			<link>https://www.moia.io/en/blog/ridepooling-in-europe</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<span>
				08.03.2024
			</span>
			The benefits of ridepooling are being increasingly utilised. Between 2019 and 2022, the number of on-demand transport services in Germany grew to more than 80 - a record number. The potential is not only recognisable in Germany, but throughout Europe. We provide an overview of the European market.
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>MOIA Mobility Consulting: Can ridepooling improve the mobility system in the Styrian Central Region?</title>
			<link>https://www.moia.io/en/blog/moia-mobility-consulting-can-ridepooling-improve-the-mobility-system-in-the-styrian-central-region</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<span>
				10.02.2024
			</span>
			With the help of various analysis tools, we evaluate how ridepooling services such as MOIA work in the mobility system of a new region and contribute to sustainable mobility. But how does such a process work? We will show you using our project in the Styrian Central Region in Austria.
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
