<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<title>Eve Blog | evehome.com</title>
		<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog</link>
		<description>All things Eve &amp; HomeKit</description>
		<generator>website-stalker https://github.com/EdJoPaTo/website-stalker</generator>
		<item>
			<title>HomeKit Over Thread With HomePod mini and Eve</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog/homekit-over-thread</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Thread

A smart home without any limitations: discover how HomePod mini, Eve and Thread bring your smart home to the next level.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Suspend your watering schedule based on the rain forecast</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog/eve-aqua-shortcuts</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Use Cases
Eve App
HomeKit

In conjunction with the Shortcuts app from Apple, the Eve app lets you suspend the watering schedules stored on your Eve Aqua if the weather is going to take a turn for the worse. All you need to do is to install the built-in shortcut right from within the Eve app.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Safeguard your home against break-in with HomeKit</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog/safeguard-your-home-against-break-in-with-homekit</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Use Cases
HomeKit

Burglars love nothing more than poorly lit and less-frequented places as it helps them stay stealthy. Given that it’s dark most of the time, in the northern hemisphere anyway, in the fall and winter, it makes it all the more important to protect your home against any attempted break-ins.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>10 tips for a smart fall and winter season with Eve</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog/tips-fall-winter</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Product Features

With technology from Eve, your smart home stays cozy, energy-efficient and secure – even when it's cold and dark outside. These tips for smart heating and lighting as well as indoor and outdoor surveillance show you which settings you need to make to achieve this quickly and easily.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>All Features of Eve Thermo Control</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/all-features-eve-thermo-control</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Product Features

With the external temperature sensor and controller Eve Thermo Control, the fourth-generation Eve Thermo smart radiator valve becomes a turnkey solution that delivers your comfort temperature exactly where you prefer to be in the room.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>New: Control Matter devices from Eve directly and locally from your iPhone, without a home hub</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog/iOS-18</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Product Features

iOS 18 is a comprehensive update that contains a number of improvements for Eve devices under Apple Home. In particular, getting started is easier than ever: with iOS 18 and an iPhone 15 Pro (and later), selected Eve devices can now be added and controlled locally and directly. A home hub is not required.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cut your power consumption at home in three simple steps</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog/cut-your-power-consumption-with-eve-energy</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Use Cases

While technological progress and legislation have cut the power consumption of many household appliances, the onslaught of new types of devices that are always on, such as smart speakers, smart TVs and Wi-Fi range extenders, threatens to wipe out all the gains made. So, what can you do?]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Automate your festive lights – based on presence</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog/automate-your-festive-lights-with-eve-energy-and-eve-motion</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Use Cases
HomeKit

Make the holiday season magical by following our tips on how to create the perfect mood.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Eve Thermo: Understanding and adjusting Temperature Offset</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog/eve-thermo-temperatur-offset</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Product Features

Eve Thermo relies on the proven technology of Hessian specialist Eurotronic for heat regulation, which works in the heating controllers of many leading smart home providers. Leveraging HomeKit as well as Eve technologies, Eurotronic's drive and control algorithm ensure comfort and efficiency. This makes saving energy easy.  We're introducing you here to a hardware feature important for heat regulation: The adjustable Temperature Offset.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Smart heating in three easy steps</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog/smart-heating-in-three-easy-steps</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Product Features

Lower heating bills with smart thermostats. Saving heating energy is the order of the day, and smart technology is ideal for this. We'll show you how to use your iPhone to convert your rooms to smart heating using schedules in three simple steps - install, define schedules and optimise.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Air source heat pump central heating with Eve Thermo</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog/heat-pump-central-heating-with-eve-thermo</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Use Cases

Optimising our air source heat pump central heating with Eve Thermo smart TRVs. As part of our journey to become more sustainable and reduce our carbon footprint, we installed an 18kW air source heat pump (ASHP) to replace the oil boiler in our Victorian (1850s) farmhouse in the Welsh borders.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
