<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<title>Steam Deck :: News</title>
		<link>https://www.steamdeck.com/en/news</link>
		<description>Available now.</description>
		<generator>website-stalker https://github.com/EdJoPaTo/website-stalker</generator>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: June 27th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415298372645253183</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jun 27, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed an issue preventing SteamOS from updating from version 3.6.7 when opted in to the 'Preview' update channel.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed errors while displaying certain collections for some users.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed mispositioned background glow on game capsules in grids.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed error when entering multiple words into search box
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Desktop Mode
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed "Soundtracks" and "All Games" shelves on home page applying the app type filter from the top of the games list. This would lead to Soundtracks showing no items if Soundtracks was not selected at the top of the games list, as an example.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415298372645253183" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>SteamOS 3.6.8 Beta: Updates for your Updates</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415298185446588911</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jun 26, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				Note: This update is for the Steam Deck Beta and Preview channels, and includes new features that are still being tested. You can opt into this in Settings > System > System Update Channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed an issue causing a "Update Error" message when attempting to interact with the update menu on the 'Preview' update channel.
						<br>
						<br>
						An upcoming Steam Client beta update will unstick users encountering this issue.  In the meantime, users encountering this issue wishing to switch update channels can follow the following steps:
						<ol>
							<li>
								Select Power -> Shutdown
								<br>
							</li>
							<li>
								Wait for the Steam Deck to power off
								<br>
							</li>
							<li>
								While holding the quick access menu key ("..."), turn the Steam Deck on with the power button
								<br>
							</li>
							<li>
								On the boot menu that appears, select the second option ("Previous SteamOS")
								<br>
							</li>
							<li>
								Once booted, check for updates as normal
							</li>
						</ol>
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415298185446588911" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: June 26th</title>
			<link>https://store.steampowered.com/gamerecording</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jun 26, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				Note: The Preview/Beta channel has been updated the evening of June 26 with some bug fixes. Please see below for more information.
				<br>
				<br>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					Game Recording
				</b>
				<br>
				Today we’ve launched Steam Game Recording into Beta, a new built-in system for creating and sharing your gameplay footage, that works on any game on Steam.
				<br>
				<br>
				Go to the
				<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/gamerecording" rel="noopener noreferrer">
					Game Recording website
				</a>
				to learn all about it and how to try it out.
				<br>
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Client and OS beta settings been updated to include a new "Preview" build of SteamOS when available for testing.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						New Recording & Screenshot manager
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improved startup and library performance for users with large libraries.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed collections based on friends not updating properly.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Desktop Mode
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed mispositioned background glow on hover in app grids.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed trading card hover effect
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Game Recording
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed incorrect formatting on clip cancel button in some languages.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed spurious game recording toggle and timeline marker shortcut keys being processed in some directinput8 games.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed recording of microphone.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed NaN showing in media manager confirmation dialog when deleting local screenshot.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed media manager delete button tooltip.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed Recording and screenshots context menu opening in its own window.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed default clip file name not being set in overlay file dialog.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improved display recording UI when at smaller sizes.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed deleting screenshots sometimes not immediately updating the Recordings and Screenshots grid.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed multi-select screenshot upload from the Recordings and Screenshots grids sometimes showing an error after the upload completed.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added support for non-latin character file paths for the game recording folder and exported clips locations.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						If recording is disabled, display in the overlay a button explaining it is disabled with a link to enable it, rather than a nonfunctional recording toggle button.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						(Linux) Fixed export clip dialog not allowing saving.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415298185444917153" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>SteamOS 3.6.7 Preview: Colorspaaaaace</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415298185442373286</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jun 25, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				Note: This update is for the Steam Deck Preview channel, and includes new features that are still being tested. You can opt into this in Settings > System > System Update Channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed an issue where colors could appear washed out when using Steam Remote Play as a client
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415298185442373286" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: June 24th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4352247531898708762</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jun 24, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed a potential crash when a bluetooth device pairing request times out.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a case where the battery status and "Allow wake from sleep" toggle would fail to show for supported bluetooth devices.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4352247531898708762" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
