<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<title>Steam Deck :: News</title>
		<link>https://www.steamdeck.com/en/news</link>
		<description>Available now.</description>
		<generator>website-stalker https://github.com/EdJoPaTo/website-stalker</generator>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Client Update: July 16th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4517756980044337063</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jul 16, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Stable channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed an issue where demos would not show a play button after changing accounts.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4517756980044337063" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: July 16th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4517756980044068772</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jul 16, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Improvements to keyboard event tracking and audio latency in updated SDL build
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improved timeout logic when establishing initial connection from UI layer to steam client's API layer
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improved client startup performance
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed controller input no longer going to game after resuming from sleep if a wake movie is set.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed broken thumbnail for screenshots from non-steam game shortcuts uploaded to steam, when viewed from another computer
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a case that game server / server browser lists would re-fetch when only re-ping on existing list was requested
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a crash that could occur at exit while cleaning up websockets
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed some games with achievements showing as "No Achievements" when sorting grids or shelves by achievement percentage.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed certain apps disappearing from Recent Games after a client restart.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Game Recording
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Improved thumbnail smoothness when mouse tracking across different highlights / regions on the timeline
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added a max framerate setting. Currently supports 30 or 60 fps.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed issue preventing default .mp4 file extension from being applied to user saved files if the user did not type an extension along with the filename
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a bug causing the live timeline edge to deviate from the actual live edge of the current recording
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a bug that caused clips to lose their thumbnails when sent from one computer to another.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed game timeline markers not being downloaded in rare cases.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Desktop Mode
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed Ctrl-F not focusing search box in library
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Clock and Timer
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						New Clock app in the Steam Overlay that can optionally be pinned on top of games.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improved Timer UI.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Big Picture
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Add warnings to game recording overlay page when broadcasting / remote playing
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Remote Play
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Simplify encoding options to a hardware encoding enable checkbox
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Steam Input
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed for SIAPI GetMotionData not returning any information on every controller but the first one plugged in.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fix for Okami HD Brush and Fishing Rod game actions
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				Note: This beta was re-released with additional changes:
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed save file dialog in overlay sometimes replacing part of the file name with the file extension.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed an issue where demos would not show a play button after changing accounts.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4517756980044068772" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: July 10th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415299511823893810</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jul 10, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed a bug that could cause some local screenshots not to appear in the media manager, if the user had few screenshots saved to steam
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a bug that could delete a workshop file if the file had failed a file validation check and had been reacquired
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a bug that could leave some local screenshots undeleted after attempting to delete multiple at one time
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Game Recording
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Improvements to UI behaviors when finalizing the beginning and end of a clip
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						No longer warp the play head to the beginning/end of a clip when setting the beginning/end of a clip via the UI buttons
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a bug where using the hotkey to add a user marker would drop the marker at the wrong location
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Increased the minimum background recording time to 15 minutes, to give the user time to edit recent clips before the recorded video ages out
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added a warning to the user if game recording has been turned off to prioritize broadcasting
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Ignore user marker shortcut key if game recording is disabled
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added the ability to save a specific frame of a video as a steam screenshot
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improved default naming of clip files to improve readability and sortability. Steam will also scan game state descriptions to apply to default clip filename, if available
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed an exception thrown if the user canceled a clip save in the file picker dialog
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Updated message displayed when there is no recent other session where the user can send a clip
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415299511823893810" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: July 2nd</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415298705122049152</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jul 2, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					Game Recording
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed bug that prevented creating clips from working on exFAT filesystems.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a couple of cases that could cause an empty entry to appear in the Post-Game Summary on a game's library page, instead of a background recording highlight.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Desktop Mode
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed collection names not being editable.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415298705122049152" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: June 28th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415298372648962795</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jun 28, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					Game Recording
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed bug that prevented Send To Phone from working if the user had not also signed in from a second desktop machine.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Desktop Mode
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed Recordings & Screenshots dialog context menu sometimes opening in new window.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed file extension not being applied automatically when saving files.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4415298372648962795" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
