<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<title>Steam Deck :: News</title>
		<link>https://www.steamdeck.com/en/news</link>
		<description>Available now.</description>
		<generator>website-stalker https://github.com/EdJoPaTo/website-stalker</generator>
		<item>
			<title>SteamOS 3.6.9 Beta: Megafixer</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4513255283370098037</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Aug 7, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				Note: This update is for the Steam Deck Beta and Preview channels, and includes new features that are still being tested. You can opt into this in Settings > System > System Update Channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Improved recovery from situations where the Steam installation could get corrupted
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed the frame limiter not properly applying in certain situations
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed certain specific refresh rates failing to apply on the OLED Limited Edition model
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed an issue where block corruption could appear on screen on certain state transitions
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Slightly improved cold boot time
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed an issue where updating the built-in controller firmware could result in a blank screen during boot
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed rare situations where switching to Desktop Mode or back could result in a blank screen, or wrong colors
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a regression with Simplified Chinese IME
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a rare issue where sound output could be corrupted on certain boots
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed Zenity dialog boxes in Desktop Mode
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						openssh: Fix remote code execution bug (CVE-2024-6387)
					</li>
				</ul>
				<b>
					External Display
				</b>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed several issues where an external display could remain blank after resuming
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed an issue where an external display could remain blank if its mode required chroma subsampling
					</li>
				</ul>
				<b>
					Input
				</b>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed an issue where DualShock 4 and DualSense controllers would sometimes not function properly on their first connection
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added support for the ASUS ROG Raikiri Pro controller
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added support for the Machenike G5 Pro controller
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed calibration on some third-party DualShock 4 controllers
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added support for the Steam Deck motion sensors to the built-in non-Steam kernel driver
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added support for extra ROG Ally keys
					</li>
				</ul>
				<b>
					OLED firmware 112
				</b>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Added support for the Windows Bluetooth driver
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4513255283370098037" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: July 30th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4513254648320322043</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jul 30, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						The friends list will now show a Steam Deck icon, instead of a gamepad icon, if the other user is playing on a Steam Deck
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Replaced the friends list VR icon with a new graphic that also matches the in-game or online friend state color
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a few spots where tooltips were causing unexpected word wrap
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Game Recording Beta
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed instances of failing to capture video data after multiple game launches.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed cropped video capture when an external display is connected or disconnected after startup.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Recordings & Screenshots
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed error that could happen when opening the Recordings & Screenshots dialog before necessary data had loaded in
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added support for "Send to Phone" share option to screenshots
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4513254648320322043" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: July 26th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4513254014350467571</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jul 26, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					Game Recording Beta
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed an issue preventing recordings from working when the device boots up offline
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Game Recording Beta - Desktop Mode
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed some timeline UI blocking mouse clicks to seek the video player
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed mouse cursor changing styles when dragging clip start and end range markers
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Slight improvement to the time it takes to generate a video thumbnail when hovering over the timeline
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4513254014350467571" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: July 23rd</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4513254014339923764</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jul 23, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed collection names being displayed in all uppercase in edit controls.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Steam Input
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						SIAPI: Fix for analog actions from other action sets incorrectly reporting as active. This affected some titles including Okami HD.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added "Rotate Output" slider to "Joystick" and "Joystick Mouse" mode settings. This can be useful for certain shmups, or simply to find a more natural "Up" direction on your joystick.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4513254014339923764" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: July 19th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4517757187692809078</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Jul 19, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed formatting of links in news posts
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a beta client only issue where a game may freeze while trying to set an achievement. This could affect games such as Elden Ring and Dark Souls.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Game Recording
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Improved the display of background recordings in the Post Game Summary on library game pages, especially for footage recorded at 21:9 or wider aspect ratios.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Desktop Mode
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Timer UI updated to use icons for buttons so that it works better across all languages.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Timer no longer has a Clear button since the new UI doesn't need it.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4517757187692809078" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
