<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<title>Steam Deck :: News</title>
		<link>https://www.steamdeck.com/en/news</link>
		<description>Available now.</description>
		<generator>website-stalker https://github.com/EdJoPaTo/website-stalker</generator>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: September 17th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/6610810473932840458</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Sep 17, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				The Steam Deck Client Beta has been updated with the following changes:
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					Steam Input
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed case where virtual menus may be left visible when mode shifting.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed Steam overlay sometimes toggling when activating on-screen keyboard from controller chord.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/6610810473932840458" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: September 16th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/6610810473929778510</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Sep 16, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				The Steam Deck Client Beta has been updated with the following changes:
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed a rare case where the UI could get stuck showing a loading throbber at startup while in Offline Mode.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed startup movie intermittently failing to play at launch.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/6610810473929778510" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>SteamOS 3.6.13 Beta: Super Lucky</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/6610810166136097143</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Sep 13, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				Note: This update is for the Steam Deck Beta and Preview channels, and includes new features that are still being tested. You can opt into this in Settings > System > System Update Channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed a problem where a Game Recording capture failing could cause subsequent captures to also fail
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed display regressions with certain titles such as Warriors All-Stars, Disgaea 5 Complete, Vampire: The Masquerade - Reckoning of New York
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/6610810166136097143" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: September 13th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/6610810166135847729</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Sep 13, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				The Steam Deck Client Beta has been updated with the following changes:
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed game recording not working for non-Steam games.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed instances where post-game events for the new Game Recording feature could show outside of the Steam Client Beta.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Steam Input
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed controller input sometimes becoming unresponsive after changing the Switch controller layout setting.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/6610810166135847729" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Client Update: September 11th</title>
			<link>https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/593110/view/4605582245626919823?snr=2_groups_partnerevents_</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Sep 11, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Stable channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					Note:
				</b>
				This update was re-released September 13th with these additional changes:
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed instances where post-game events for the new Game Recording feature could show outside of the Steam Client Beta.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed controller input sometimes becoming unresponsive after changing the Switch controller layout setting.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Steam Families is now available for all users. For more info about Steam Families, you can read our
						<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/news/app/593110/view/4605582245626919823?snr=2_groups_partnerevents_" rel="noopener noreferrer">
							news post
						</a>
						, check out our
						<a href="https://help.steampowered.com/en/faqs/view/054C-3167-DD7F-49D4" rel="noopener noreferrer">
							Support FAQ
						</a>
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added a dropdown to Settings->Display->Advanced to select the maximum resolution allowed to be used by games. This is the global version of the 'Game Resolution' dropdown already available under Game Settings->General.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added Sign Out to the power menu on Deck.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						The friends list will now show a Steam Deck icon, instead of a gamepad icon, if the other user is playing on a Steam Deck
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Replaced the friends list VR icon with a new graphic that also matches the in-game or online friend state color
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improvements to keyboard event tracking and audio latency in updated SDL build
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improved client startup performance
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improved reliability of "games in common" collections in library
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed controller input no longer going to game after resuming from sleep if a wake movie is set.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed broken thumbnail for screenshots from non-steam game shortcuts uploaded to steam, when viewed from another computer
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a case that game server / server browser lists would re-fetch when only re-ping on existing list was requested
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed some games with achievements showing as "No Achievements" when sorting grids or shelves by achievement percentage.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed certain apps disappearing from Recent Games after a client restart
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed formatting of links in news posts
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed collection names being displayed in all uppercase in edit controls
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a few spots where tooltips were causing unexpected word wrap
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed an issue with padding for friends in the game invite dialog
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Screenshots
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Redesigned the screenshots manager
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added easier ways to share screenshots directly from Steam, including:
						<br>
						<ul>
							<li>
								Copy directly to your clipboard
								<br>
							</li>
							<li>
								Send to friend or chat group via Steam chat
								<br>
							</li>
							<li>
								Send to your phone via the Steam Mobile App
								<br>
							</li>
							<li>
								Export as a new file on your computer
							</li>
						</ul>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improved the performance and reliability of the screenshots manager
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added the ability to search within the app filter dropdown
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Pre-emptive work to provide future support for recordings and clips to integrate with the screenshots manager when
						<a href="https://store.steampowered.com/gamerecording" rel="noopener noreferrer">
							Steam Game Recording
						</a>
						releases out of beta
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Desktop Mode
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed Ctrl-F not focusing search box in library
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Clock and Timer
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						New Clock app in the Steam Overlay that can optionally be pinned on top of games.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improved Timer UI.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Remote Play
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Simplify encoding options to a hardware encoding enable checkbox
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Steam Input
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Reduce CPU usage when using both Gyro and Joystick or Trackpad for mouse input
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed for SIAPI GetMotionData not returning any information on every controller but the first one plugged in.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fix for Okami HD Brush and Fishing Rod game actions
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						SIAPI: Fix for analog actions from other action sets incorrectly reporting as active. This affected some titles including Okami HD.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added "Rotate Output" slider to "Joystick" and "Joystick Mouse" mode settings. This can be useful for certain shmups, or simply to find a more natural "Up" direction on your joystick.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Added Output Icons to all Mode/Behavior dropdown menus. These indicate if the mode (by default) generates OS Mouse output, XInput (controller) Output, Steam Input API Action Output, or is a remapping tool/Overlay Menu (Touch, Radial, Hotbar).
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Steam Input API Analog Actions that can have multiple modes i.e. "Camera | Camera as FlickStick" are now labelled as "... (via FlickStick)"
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Steam Input API Analog Actions can now optionally be used "... (via Gyro To Mouse)" (default is still "As Mouse" or "As Joystick Mouse" depending on source).
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fix rare issue where Gyro Processing occurred before controller type is established.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fix for Track Pad as Button Behavior not displaying any glyphs.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fix "Gyro Calibration" Button appearing twice on Gyro config screen if there is a mode shift applied to the Gyro.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed regression: "Dots per 360" was having no effect on FlickStick or Gyro to Mouse modes
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a bug where PlayStation controllers connected over BT could be shown as connected over USB
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a case where exiting a non-Steam game could leave controllers w/o input until you hit the guide button or QAM button
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4754201033330491054" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
