<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<title>Steam Deck :: News</title>
		<link>https://www.steamdeck.com/en/news</link>
		<description>Available now.</description>
		<generator>website-stalker/0.22.0 https://github.com/EdJoPaTo/website-stalker</generator>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Client Update: February 27th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4338726151304267515</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Feb 27, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Stable (default) channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Updated embedded Chromium build in Steam, clearing path for further updates soon.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improved UI performance while navigating Steam interface.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Updated the quick access performance menu with descriptions for each setting, including how they affect the system and the expected power/performance/visual quality tradeoffs.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Triggering a Factory Reset will now install a clean version of the OS in addition to deleting user data if the OS image has been modified.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Improved performance when adding/removing multiple games to/from Family View in the library.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Corrected height of low battery notification.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Removed duplicate friend counter on game capsules.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a case where the sdcard was set as the default install location on reboot.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a case where the network status icon would fail to render for virtual networks.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed store button on main menu remaining disabled in Family View even if store permissions were granted to the account.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed creation of erroneous steamwebhelper processes when steamwebhelper crashes.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed on-screen text input to show the game in the background.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed downloading content with long file names in some cases.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a case where the client could get stuck in the shutting down screen.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a case where no element would be selected in the UI when closing the quick access menu.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed CD Keys popup not appearing during launch for games that request it.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed failing to switch to Japanese keyboard layout.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed some extraneous disk reads that could impact performance.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed game news sometimes appearing out of order in game details activity feed.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed miscellaneous regressions in the screenshot manager.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed wide game images sometimes failing to load.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed custom logo positions sometimes not applying on app details pages.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Steam Input
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Added a setting for the player LED for DualSense controllers.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Controllers can be used to dismiss/continue when controller support information panels appear before a game's launch.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						QoL: Gyro Calibration button available in Controller Config Quick settings, and in the Gyro section of the Controller Layout Editor.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed styling of the controller mode settings page.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed Gyro enable button not being respected.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed occasionally creating an extra virtual controller that is non-responsive.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Friends & Chat
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed a case where group chats could get stuck on "Requesting Group Chat Information" after reconnecting to Steam.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Remote Play
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed missing performance graph while streaming.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Desktop Mode
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Stopped showing ready-to-play icon on Recent Games shelf, which does not filter to ready-to-play.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed user avatar in title bar momentarily switching back to default during startup.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a case where mouse click input could stop working when starting to drag operation on a steam window.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed main Steam window re-opening when closed if small mode has been entered or exited.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed Steam windows sometimes freezing until resized.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed maximize/restore button and window resize grip not updating properly.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed "My Games" collection also including games borrowed from other users.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed opacity of play bar on game details pages.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed overlay notes window controls scrolling off the top and new note/delete note buttons not being visible.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed mouse cursor jumping when some browser windows are closed or hidden.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4338726151304267515" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: February 22nd</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4338725580145248447</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Feb 22, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed some Steam chat views not indicating which item was selected
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Steam Input
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fix styling of the controller mode settings page
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4338725580145248447" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: February 20th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4338725580138075821</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Feb 20, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed creation of erroneous steamwebhelper processes when steamwebhelper crashes
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed on-screen text input to show the game in the background.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed EULA dialog extending off the screen
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed friends list not showing which friend was selected
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Desktop Mode
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed user avatar in title bar momentarily switching back to default during startup.
					</li>
				</ul>
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4338725580138075821" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: February 16th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/7198510808230796455</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Feb 16, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed downloading content with long file names in some cases.
						<br>
					</li>
					<li>
						Fixed a case where the client could get stuck in the shutting down screen.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				Note: this client was re-released to fix excessive file access on shutdown.
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/7198510808230796455" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Steam Deck Beta Client Update: February 14th</title>
			<link>https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4365746543858878934</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		<div>
			<h5>
				Feb 14, 2024
			</h5>
			<div>
				We have just shipped an updated Steam Deck Client to the Preview/Beta channel.
				<br>
				<br>
				<b>
					General
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed a case where no element would be selected in the UI when closing the quick access menu.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Desktop Mode
				</b>
				<br>
				<ul>
					<li>
						Fixed a case where mouse click input could stop working when starting to drag operation on a steam window.
					</li>
				</ul>
				<br>
				<b>
					Preview Only
				</b>
				<br>
				<br>
				As part of today’s update, we are adding SteamOS Crash Report functionality. This feature is
				<b>
					turned off by default
				</b>
				– if you’d like to help us with collecting crash reports to continue improving SteamOS, please turn it on in
				<b>
					Settings > System
				</b>
				.
				<br>
				<br>
				When this feature is enabled, if your Steam Deck crashes, it will send crash reports and system information to Valve (the next time it's connected to the internet). You will have granular control over what types of information will be sent in the settings for this feature (in Settings > System).
				<br>
				<br>
				Thank you for helping us improve SteamOS.
			</div>
			<div>
				<div>
				</div>
				<div>
					<a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/1675200/eventcomments/4365746543858878934" rel="noopener noreferrer">
						Discuss on Steam
					</a>
				</div>
			</div>
		</div>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
