<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<title>Hetzner News</title>
		<link>https://www.hetzner.com/news/</link>
		<description></description>
		<generator>website-stalker/0.19.0 https://github.com/EdJoPaTo/website-stalker</generator>
		<item>
			<title>New dedicated servers for almost any use case</title>
			<link>https://www.hetzner.com/news/neue-dedicated-server-2023/</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[15. March 2023

Hetzner’s simulataneously launching three new powerful dedicated servers, and all of them at unbeatable prices!

The new EX101 Dedicated Server from the EX line houses the high-end Intel® i9-13900 processor and…]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>HETZNER CONTINUES ITS GROWTH IN THE US WITH A NEW LOCATION</title>
			<link>https://www.hetzner.com/news/12-22-cloud-usa/</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[5. December 2022

West Coast - Here we come: Today, we officially launched our second location in the USA for cloud products in Hillsboro, Oregon, just outside of Portland, a location ripe for…]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cyber Deals: Hetzner Storage Shares and Dedicated Server AX101 in the spotlight</title>
			<link>https://www.hetzner.com/news/cyber-deals-2022/</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[25. November 2022

This year, we’re offering you a duo of deals: Cyber Deals 2022!

Starting on 28 November 2022 at 8:00 am (CET), you can order one of 2022 Hetzner Storage Shares and…]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RX-Line: Pushing the envelop of parallelization</title>
			<link>https://www.hetzner.com/news/07-22-rx-line/</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[19. July 2022

The new RX-line is now available and features the first Ampere® Altra® Arm-based dedicated servers in Europe.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hetzner Cloud: Flexible Networking</title>
			<link>https://www.hetzner.com/news/06-22-flexibles-networking/</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[28. June 2022

Three different network options are now available for cloud servers!

When you create a cloud server, it will no longer automatically include public IP addresses (IPv4, IPv6).]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>25 years of Hetzner - join the fun &amp; win one of 25 prizes!</title>
			<link>https://www.hetzner.com/news/06-22-sweepstakes/</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[1. June 2022

We're celebrating 25 years of being your home for the Internet.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Focused on a low price and strong performance: the new Hetzner Dedicated Root Server EX43</title>
			<link>https://www.hetzner.com/news/03-22-ex43/</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[22. March 2022

The Hetzner Dedicated Root Server EX43 puts the new Intel® Core™ i5-12500 processor in the spotlight. This chip is from the twelfth generation, nicknamed "Alder Lake".]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Seasons special: Skip the setup fee on selected AX servers!</title>
			<link>https://www.hetzner.com/news/03-22-seasons-special/</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[1. March 2022

We want to help you grow this spring. You can now get a Hetzner dedicated root server with an AMD Ryzen™ CPU and skip the setup fees.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Maximize performance and minimize admin overhead: The new Hetzner managed servers</title>
			<link>https://www.hetzner.com/news/02-22-managed-server/</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[21. February 2022

Enjoy the powerful performance of two new models and put the responsibility for server administration and maintenance in our hands, letting you relax and focus on your business.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hetzner Storage Share and Storage Box: Data storage and management made easy</title>
			<link>https://www.hetzner.com/news/02-22-storage/</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[7. February 2022

Making backups of your data is essential for preventing data loss.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
