<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<title>Eve Blog | evehome.com</title>
		<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog</link>
		<description>All things Eve &amp; HomeKit</description>
		<generator>website-stalker/0.20.0 https://github.com/EdJoPaTo/website-stalker</generator>
		<item>
			<title>HomeKit Over Thread With HomePod mini and Eve</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/en/blog/homekit-over-thread</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Thread

A smart home without any limitations: discover how HomePod mini, Eve and Thread bring your smart home to the next level.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cut your power consumption at home in three simple steps</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/index%2Ephp/en/taxonomy/term/59</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Use Cases

While technological progress and legislation have cut the power consumption of many household appliances, the onslaught of new types of devices that are always on, such as smart speakers, smart TVs and Wi-Fi range extenders, threatens to wipe out all the gains made. So, what can you do?]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>All features of Eve Weather</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/index%2Ephp/en/taxonomy/term/58</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Product Features

Eve Weather combines the advantages of all types of weather monitoring solutions to give you insights come rain, wind, sun, or snow. Read on to learn how to set up and get the most out of Eve Weather.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Automate your festive lights – based on presence</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/index%2Ephp/en/taxonomy/term/59</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Use Cases
HomeKit

Make the holiday season magical by following our tips on how to create the perfect mood.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Eve Thermo: Understanding and adjusting Temperature Offset</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/index%2Ephp/en/taxonomy/term/58</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Product Features

Eve Thermo relies on the proven technology of Hessian specialist Eurotronic for heat regulation, which works in the heating controllers of many leading smart home providers. Leveraging HomeKit as well as Eve technologies, Eurotronic's drive and control algorithm ensure comfort and efficiency. This makes saving energy easy.  We're introducing you here to a hardware feature important for heat regulation: The adjustable Temperature Offset.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Smart heating in three easy steps</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/index%2Ephp/en/taxonomy/term/58</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Product Features

Lower heating bills with smart thermostats. Saving heating energy is the order of the day, and smart technology is ideal for this. We'll show you how to use your iPhone to convert your rooms to smart heating using schedules in three simple steps - install, define schedules and optimise.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Air source heat pump central heating with Eve Thermo</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/index%2Ephp/en/taxonomy/term/59</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Use Cases

Optimising our air source heat pump central heating with Eve Thermo smart TRVs. As part of our journey to become more sustainable and reduce our carbon footprint, we installed an 18kW air source heat pump (ASHP) to replace the oil boiler in our Victorian (1850s) farmhouse in the Welsh borders.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Turn off the heat while ventilating: Combine Eve Thermo and Eve Door &amp; Window</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/index%2Ephp/en/taxonomy/term/59</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Use Cases

Using its built-in temperature sensor, Eve Thermo will detect sudden temperature drops. This way it can turn off the heat whenever someone opens a window.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>All features of Eve Thermo</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/index%2Ephp/en/taxonomy/term/58</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Product Features

The multi award-winning Eve Thermo smart radiator valve is quick and easy to install and set up. And with a bit of fine-tuning, it can unleash all the convenience that connected heating has to offer. Read on for a detailed overview of all the functions Eve Thermo offers.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Schedules &amp; location control: Smart heating with Eve Thermo</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/index%2Ephp/en/taxonomy/term/58</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Product Features
Eve App

Enjoy a cozy home when you’re there, and save energy when you’re not – that's smart heating, courtesy of Eve Thermo. Now it’s easier than ever to combine the sheer convenience of schedules with location-based heating. Read on to learn how to enjoy all these great benefits.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Even penguins enjoy keeping cozy thanks to smart heating in the kindergarten</title>
			<link>https://www.evehome.com/index%2Ephp/en/taxonomy/term/59</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[Use Cases

A parent-run initiative like ours consumes a great deal of time and effort, plus we need to keep a constant eye on our operating costs. However, as we don’t just want to save money, but also lighten the load on our staff and the environment, we’ve recently started using smart radiator valves to intelligently control the indoor temperature. In this post we share the lessons we’ve learned.]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
