<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<title>Inuru</title>
		<link>https://www.inuru.com/about/news</link>
		<description>Providing the latests official press releases and exclusive background information on low-cost OLED development and OLED applications.</description>
		<generator>website-stalker https://github.com/EdJoPaTo/website-stalker</generator>
		<item>
			<title>Inuru manifesto</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/inuru-manifesto</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		May 16, 2024
		<h1>
			Inuru manifesto
		</h1>
		<p>
			How Inuru fosters a world where humanity lives in balance with nature through the power of technology.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How to turn your product into an experience: Case Study on Coca-Cola X Star Wars &quot;Galactic bottles&quot; lit with Inuru OLED</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/how-to-turn-your-product-into-an-experience-case-study-on-coca-cola-x-star-wars-galactic-bottles-lit-with-inuru-oled</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Apr 30, 2024
		<h1>
			How to turn your product into an experience: Case Study on Coca-Cola X Star Wars "Galactic bottles" lit with Inuru OLED
		</h1>
		<p>
			In this post series we would like to shed light on how to turn your product into an experience, by including light and animation with into your products to make them ready to the new era of consumers.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How to Use Interactive Labels with OLED Technology in Marketing Campaigns Effectively</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/how-to-use-interactive-labels-with-oled-technology-in-marketing-campaigns-effectively</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Mar 21, 2024
		<h1>
			How to Use Interactive Labels with OLED Technology in Marketing Campaigns Effectively
		</h1>
		<p>
			Light is all about visibility and the structure that follows it. Despite living in a digital, data driven world, we still seem to live in the dark, when it comes down to creating a successful marketing or branding campaign. In the dynamic and ever-changing world of marketing, customers are inundated with various types of content—primarily on social media, television, and even in real life—the challenge lies in crafting a successful and attention-grabbing marketing campaign, in a world that has seen it all on TikTok. In the past, we have been working with the world’s best brands and their marketing geniuses, that all utilized our technology to create captivating events and strategically position products in new channels. Reviewing these campaigns today we can see a clear structure on what is successful and not. Today, we want to share this knowledge with you on how to make run a successful in the new era of digitization and Gen-Z coming into the market. In this article, we will analyze the successful marketing campaigns mentioned earlier. We’ll examine the factors that contributed to their success and explore areas where improvements could have been made. Let’s delve deeper into this topic.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Digital Fashion and the Metaverse Change the Clothes We Will Wear</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/how-digital-fashion-and-the-metaverse-change-the-clothes-we-will-wear</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jan 17, 2024
		<h1>
			How Digital Fashion and the Metaverse Change the Clothes We Will Wear
		</h1>
		<p>
			This article elaborates the hype behind digital fashion and how the today consumers digital experience will influence the design of fashion in the future. This article is for fashion designers and manufacturers who want to shape clothing and fashion of tomorrow.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Future of Board Games: A Journey from OLED Dreams to Reality</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/the-future-of-board-games-a-journey-from-oled-dreams-to-reality</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Dec 21, 2023
		<h1>
			The Future of Board Games: A Journey from OLED Dreams to Reality
		</h1>
		<p>
			Revolutionizing Board Games with OLED: From Fantasy to Reality – Discover how Inuru's OLED technology is transforming traditional board games into immersive, interactive experiences, starting with 'Streaks' by Buffalo Games.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Inuru makes OLEDs affordable</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/low-cost-oleds-for-low-cost-oled-labels-and-mass-market-adoption</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Oct 4, 2023
		<h1>
			How Inuru makes OLEDs affordable
		</h1>
		<p>
			How we make OLEDs affordable to bring OLED labels to mass market applications.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Organic Lighting Technology Make Everyday Objects Smart like Medical Packaging and Expiry Date Indications</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/how-organic-lighting-technology-make-everyday-objects-smart-like-medical-packaging-and-expiry-date-indications</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Sep 5, 2023
		<h1>
			How Organic Lighting Technology Make Everyday Objects Smart like Medical Packaging and Expiry Date Indications
		</h1>
		<p>
			This posts describes the use of organic lighting technologies (OLED) for medical applications.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What it takes to make Smart Packaging become reality</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/what-it-takes-to-make-smart-packaging-become-reality</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Apr 3, 2023
		<h1>
			What it takes to make Smart Packaging become reality
		</h1>
		<p>
			For 30 years, smart packaging has been an idea that has failed to achieve larger market adoption and has generally been underwhelming despite various companies' attempts. Inuru's latest generation of luminous labels have been launched with CATTIER's brand reboot for Glamour, impressing even one of the oldest Champagne houses in the world. Our labels have all the necessary characteristics for market-ready solutions, and we discuss our key deliverables for smart packaging.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The plan behind Inuru</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/the-plan-behind-inuru</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jun 10, 2022
		<h1>
			The plan behind Inuru
		</h1>
		<p>
			Why we have founded Inuru. The reason why we have invested 10 years to develop printed light.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>&quot;Light Is the New Black&quot;: Program Announced for WORLD OLED DEVELOPERS CONFERENCE on 24th June in Berlin</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/light-is-the-new-black-oledcon</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jun 3, 2025
		<h1>
			"Light Is the New Black": Program Announced for WORLD OLED DEVELOPERS CONFERENCE on 24th June in Berlin
		</h1>
		<p>
			Experience visionary designs by Clara Daguin and try on real OLED-embedded clothing. From haute couture to smart workwear—light is the new black in wearable tech.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>First World OLED Developers Conference Announced</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/first-world-oled-developers-conference</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		May 20, 2025
		<h1>
			First World OLED Developers Conference Announced
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru is organizing its first-ever World OLED Developers Conference, bringing together designers, engineers, and creators to explore recent advancements in OLED technology. The event will highlight Inuru’s novel OLED manufacturing method, enabling cost-effective production of OLED lighting and displays in any shape or color. It also focuses on integrating OLEDs into various products, including packaging, textiles, and automotive parts. Attendees will participate in workshops, view demonstrations, and engage in shaping the roadmap from OLED illumination to complex display systems.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>We print displays-Inuru Prints Active Matrix OLED Display</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/we-print-displays-inuru-prints-active-matrix-oled-display</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		May 6, 2025
		<h1>
			We print displays-Inuru Prints Active Matrix OLED Display
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru, a leading European OLED display manufacturer, has achieved a major breakthrough by successfully printing OLED displays in three separate colors using its current-generation technology. Based in Berlin/Wildau, Germany, Inuru has confirmed its compatibility with active matrix backplanes—the standard for modern high-resolution screens—paving the way for affordable, flexible displays in packaging, wearables, and smart appliances. This milestone positions Inuru among the most innovative display manufacturers in Europe, offering printed OLED solutions beyond traditional TV and smartphone applications.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Engelbert Strauss Introduces Backpack with Inuru OLED Technology</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/engelbert-strauss-introduces-backpack-with-inuru-oled-technology</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Oct 11, 2024
		<h1>
			Engelbert Strauss Introduces Backpack with Inuru OLED Technology
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru's OLED Technology Adopted in Clothing and Workwear as Engelbert Strauss Introduces Backpack with Inuru OLED Technology
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Coca-Cola Introduces Light-Up Packaging using OLED from Dragon Factory in Partnership with Marvel and Rappi</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/coca-cola-introduces-light-up-packaging-using-oled-from-dragon-factory-in-partnership-with-marvel-and-rappi</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jul 22, 2024
		<h1>
			Coca-Cola Introduces Light-Up Packaging using OLED from Dragon Factory in Partnership with Marvel and Rappi
		</h1>
		<p>
			Coca-Cola Unveils Limited-Edition Thor Beverage with Inuru’s OLED Technology in Exclusive Collaboration with Marvel and Rappi
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Inuru Opens New Customer Experience Department in Warsaw</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/inuru-opens-new-customer-experience-department-in-warsaw</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jul 7, 2024
		<h1>
			Inuru Opens New Customer Experience Department in Warsaw
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru's new Warsaw location to enhance customer interaction and accelerate OLED innovation with dedicated design and production units.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Caviar Lianozoff uses Inuru OLED labels for luxury branding</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/caviar-lianozoff-uses-inuru-oled-labels-for-luxury-branding</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Apr 10, 2024
		<h1>
			Caviar Lianozoff uses Inuru OLED labels for luxury branding
		</h1>
		<p>
			Caviar Lianozoff unveils Lumière, integrating Inuru OLED labels for a luxury branding and premium products experience.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Coca Cola Company explores Inuru OLED labels</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/the-coca-cola-company-explores-inuru-oled-labels</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Dec 21, 2018
		<h1>
			The Coca Cola Company explores Inuru OLED labels
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru releases world's first OLED label with The-Coca-Cola-Company.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Inuru launches low-cost OLED mass production at Dragon Factory Berlin-Brandeburg</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/inuru-launches-oled-mass-production-near-berlin</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Mar 11, 2024
		<h1>
			Inuru launches low-cost OLED mass production at Dragon Factory Berlin-Brandeburg
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru launches low cost OLED mass production.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Inuru Announces Opening of Revolutionary Dragon Factory: A New Era in OLED Technology</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/inuru-announces-opening-of-revolutionary-dragon-factory-a-new-era-in-oled-technology</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Feb 1, 2024
		<h1>
			Inuru Announces Opening of Revolutionary Dragon Factory: A New Era in OLED Technology
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru, a pioneer in OLED technology, proudly announces the grand opening of the Dragon Factory, the world’s first facility dedicated to the low-cost production of printed OLED lighting and displays.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Buffalo Games and Inuru release the First Game Board with OLED Lighting  &apos;Streaks&apos;,</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/buffalo-games-and-inuru-announce-revolutionary-collaboration-introducing-streaks-the-first-game-board-with-oled-lighting</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Dec 5, 2023
		<h1>
			Buffalo Games and Inuru release the First Game Board with OLED Lighting  'Streaks',
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru expands into Toy industry with first OLED board-game.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Displate and Inuru Announce Partnership to Bring Unique User Experience through OLED Technology</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/displate-and-inuru-announce-partnership-for-animated-luminous-posters</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Apr 7, 2023
		<h1>
			Displate and Inuru Announce Partnership to Bring Unique User Experience through OLED Technology
		</h1>
		<p>
			Displate and Inuru have partnered to create a new product category called LUMINO.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cattier Introduces Luminous Champagne Labels with Inuru.</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/cattier-uses-luminous-labels-for-champagne</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Oct 1, 2023
		<h1>
			Cattier Introduces Luminous Champagne Labels with Inuru.
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru teams up with Packhelp to deliver high quality marketing solutions.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
