<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<title>Inuru</title>
		<link>https://www.inuru.com/about/news</link>
		<description>Providing the latests official press releases and exclusive background information on low-cost OLED development and OLED applications.</description>
		<generator>website-stalker https://github.com/EdJoPaTo/website-stalker</generator>
		<item>
			<title>Why Packaging Design Must Work Without Images in 2026</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/why-packaging-design-must-work-without-images-in-2026</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Feb 6, 2026
		<h1>
			Why Packaging Design Must Work Without Images in 2026
		</h1>
		<p>
			Packaging design must work without images in 2026 because most brand discovery now happens in small formats where photography becomes unreadable. Thumbnails, feeds and search previews compress visuals so heavily that type-first, abstract and high-contrast layouts deliver better recognition, clarity and recall than photo-dependent packs.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Flat vs Dimensional Packaging Design in 2026: Performance, Visibility, and What Works Best for Shelf and Digital</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/flat-vs-dimensional-packaging-design-2026</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Feb 4, 2026
		<h1>
			Flat vs Dimensional Packaging Design in 2026: Performance, Visibility, and What Works Best for Shelf and Digital
		</h1>
		<p>
			Flat and dimensional packaging represent two core visual strategies used to communicate brand meaning across shelf and screen. Flat design relies on simplified forms and strong contrast, making it highly effective in fast-scroll digital environments. Dimensional design uses shadows, depth cues and hierarchy to attract attention in physical retail. In 2026, the most successful packaging systems blend these approaches using flat structures for recognition and designed depth to create focus, visibility and cross-channel consistency.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Packaging Trends 2026 and Beyond - An AI-Informed Analysis by Inuru</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/packaging-trends-2026-beyond</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jan 30, 2026
		<h1>
			Packaging Trends 2026 and Beyond - An AI-Informed Analysis by Inuru
		</h1>
		<p>
			Packaging is shifting from static visuals to intelligent, sensory-driven experiences. Discover the key trends shaping 2026 and beyond including the rise of Active Packaging Interfaces powered by printed OLED light.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Gen Z Is Shaping Packaging Design in 2026: What Really Changes and What Still Matters</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/gen-z-packaging-design-2026</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jan 26, 2026
		<h1>
			How Gen Z Is Shaping Packaging Design in 2026: What Really Changes and What Still Matters
		</h1>
		<p>
			A research-driven analysis of how Gen Z influences packaging design in 2026. This article separates real behavioral impact from hype, compares Gen Z with Millennials, Gen X and Boomers, and explains how brands can design packaging that performs across generations while meeting new expectations for clarity, transparency and value.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What Does It Mean to Design Packaging for Speed? How Brands Win Attention in One Second</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/designing-packaging-for-speed</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jan 22, 2026
		<h1>
			What Does It Mean to Design Packaging for Speed? How Brands Win Attention in One Second
		</h1>
		<p>
			In 2026, packaging must communicate what it is and why it matters within a single second, across shelves, screens and constant motion.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Color Works in Packaging Design: Why Bold, Emotional Palettes Are Replacing Neutral Ones</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/color-in-packaging-design-2026</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jan 20, 2026
		<h1>
			How Color Works in Packaging Design: Why Bold, Emotional Palettes Are Replacing Neutral Ones
		</h1>
		<p>
			This article explains how color functions as a strategic design system in packaging and why bold, emotionally legible palettes are replacing neutral ones by 2026.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Typography-Led Packaging: Why Letters Are Becoming the Primary Brand Signal in 2026</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/typography-led-packaging-2026</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jan 14, 2026
		<h1>
			Typography-Led Packaging: Why Letters Are Becoming the Primary Brand Signal in 2026
		</h1>
		<p>
			Typography-led packaging is a 2026 design shift where letterforms replace logos and graphics as the primary brand signal. This article explores why typography outperforms imagery in human cognition, shelf recognition, and cross-channel consistency and how type becomes the brand itself.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What Is Human Packaging Design? Why Texture, Illustration, and Imperfection Matter in 2026</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/what-is-human-packaging-design</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jan 13, 2026
		<h1>
			What Is Human Packaging Design? Why Texture, Illustration, and Imperfection Matter in 2026
		</h1>
		<p>
			Human packaging design is a strategic response to AI-driven visual sameness. This article explains why texture, illustration, and intentional imperfection become commercial trust and recognition signals in 2026 helping brands stand out on shelf and in digital environments.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Proof-First Packaging Claims: How Brands Communicate Sustainability Without Greenwashing</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/proof-first-packaging-claims-sustainability-without-greenwashing-2026</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jan 9, 2026
		<h1>
			Proof-First Packaging Claims: How Brands Communicate Sustainability Without Greenwashing
		</h1>
		<p>
			In 2026, sustainability communication shifts from broad promises to proof-first packaging claims. Brands reduce claims, focus on verifiable improvements, and position sustainability as performance and economic intelligence rather than moral signaling.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What Is Connected Packaging? How QR and 2D Codes Turn Packaging into a Marketing Channel</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/what-is-connected-packaging</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jan 5, 2026
		<h1>
			What Is Connected Packaging? How QR and 2D Codes Turn Packaging into a Marketing Channel
		</h1>
		<p>
			Connected packaging uses QR and 2D codes to link physical products with digital experiences. As the shift from 1D barcodes to 2D codes accelerates ahead of Sunrise 2027, packaging becomes an interactive, measurable, and owned marketing channel that extends beyond the shelf and into everyday use.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What Is Recyclable-by-Design Packaging? The 2026 Shift Toward Simpler Packaging</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/recyclable-by-design-packaging-2026</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jan 2, 2026
		<h1>
			What Is Recyclable-by-Design Packaging? The 2026 Shift Toward Simpler Packaging
		</h1>
		<p>
			Recyclable-by-design packaging is the new baseline in 2026. Learn why simpler packaging builds trust, reduces friction, and how brands can simplify structures and visuals without sacrificing shelf visibility or brand nuance.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Do You Want to Illuminate Your Brand? How to Choose the Right Lighting Technology for Labels</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/illuminate-your-brand-choosing-lighting-technology-labels</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Dec 30, 2025
		<h1>
			Do You Want to Illuminate Your Brand? How to Choose the Right Lighting Technology for Labels
		</h1>
		<p>
			Illuminated labels can elevate a product but only if the light matches the brand. This article explains how OLED, LED, and EL technologies differ in light quality, integration, functionality, safety, and scalability, and how to choose the right solution based on what role light should play in your brand, not just on technical specifications.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What Is OLED? A Practical Definition and How Printed OLEDs Expand Its Use</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/what-is-oled-printed-oled-manufacturing</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Dec 18, 2025
		<h1>
			What Is OLED? A Practical Definition and How Printed OLEDs Expand Its Use
		</h1>
		<p>
			A clear, manufacturer-level explanation of what OLED is, how it works, and how printed OLED manufacturing expands its use beyond displays into packaging and wearables.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Why Subtle Visual Signals Win in an Overstimulated World: The Micro-Emotion Advantage</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/subtle-visual-signals-micro-emotion-advantage</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Dec 12, 2025
		<h1>
			Why Subtle Visual Signals Win in an Overstimulated World: The Micro-Emotion Advantage
		</h1>
		<p>
			In an overstimulated world, subtle visual signals outperform aggressive effects. This article explores the neuroscience behind micro-emotions and explains why gentle, low-intensity cues create stronger engagement, trust, and premium perception across modern marketing environments.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Future of Shelf-Visibility: How Retail Science and Emerging Technologies Will Shape Product Discovery by 2030</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/shelf-visibility-future-retail-2030</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Dec 8, 2025
		<h1>
			The Future of Shelf-Visibility: How Retail Science and Emerging Technologies Will Shape Product Discovery by 2030
		</h1>
		<p>
			How shelf-visibility shapes product discovery—and why the next decade will rely on AI, smarter shelf design, and subtle illumination to keep products findable.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Does Light Influence Purchasing Decisions?</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/how-light-influences-purchasing-decisions</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Dec 2, 2025
		<h1>
			How Does Light Influence Purchasing Decisions?
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover how lighting shapes shopper behavior, emotion, and product perception. A scientific deep dive into how subtle illumination increases visibility, reduces decision fatigue, and influences purchasing decisions.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Touch, Motion, Light: The Role of Sensory Interaction in Modern Packaging</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/what-is-sensory-packaging</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Nov 28, 2025
		<h1>
			Touch, Motion, Light: The Role of Sensory Interaction in Modern Packaging
		</h1>
		<p>
			Sensory packaging is packaging designed to engage one or more human senses such as sight, touch, sound, or scent beyond standard visual graphics. By adding interactive or tactile elements, it creates a memorable and emotionally engaging product experience that captures attention and increases perceived value.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Personalized Light: How OLED Packaging Redefines Customer Experience in the Era of Marketing Personalization</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/personalized-light-packaging-oled</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Nov 24, 2025
		<h1>
			Personalized Light: How OLED Packaging Redefines Customer Experience in the Era of Marketing Personalization
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover how personalized light packaging using printed OLED technology creates glowing names, messages, and interactive experiences that redefine customer engagement.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Personalized Packaging: The New Frontier in Marketing Investment (2025 Report)</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/personalized-packaging-marketing-investment-2025</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Nov 18, 2025
		<h1>
			Personalized Packaging: The New Frontier in Marketing Investment (2025 Report)
		</h1>
		<p>
			How personalization, psychology, and printed OLED light reshape brand experience
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bright for the Holidays: 5 Rigid Packaging Ideas That Spark Emotion</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/bright-for-the-holidays-rigid-packaging-ideas</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Nov 13, 2025
		<h1>
			Bright for the Holidays: 5 Rigid Packaging Ideas That Spark Emotion
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover five research-based rigid packaging ideas that elevate holiday gifting through emotion, texture, and illumination. Learn how light and structure transform unboxing into a multisensory experience.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What Is Premium Packaging and How Light Is Redefining It</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/what-is-premium-packaging-and-the-role-of-light</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Oct 31, 2025
		<h1>
			What Is Premium Packaging and How Light Is Redefining It
		</h1>
		<p>
			Premium packaging is high-quality, design-driven packaging that enhances a product’s perceived value through exceptional materials, craftsmanship, and sensory storytelling. It goes beyond protection—creating an emotional connection through texture, structure, and reveal. Premium packaging expresses brand identity, quality, and exclusivity from the very first touch.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>From Bar to Gift Box: Where Glowing Details Fit in Brand Storytelling</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/from-bar-to-gift-box-glowing-details-luxury-packaging</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Oct 28, 2025
		<h1>
			From Bar to Gift Box: Where Glowing Details Fit in Brand Storytelling
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover how glowing OLED details in luxury packaging—from bar retail to gift box experiences—transform unboxing into interactive brand storytelling.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ice-Bucket-Proof Labels: What They Are, Why They Matter, and How to Design Them Right</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/ice-bucket-proof-labels</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Oct 3, 2025
		<h1>
			Ice-Bucket-Proof Labels: What They Are, Why They Matter, and How to Design Them Right
		</h1>
		<p>
			Ice-bucket-proof labels stay flat and adhered for 24–48h on ice—resisting edge-lift, wrinkles, ink failure, and greying; tested for nightlife use.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What smart tech can make bottles respond to sound or touch?</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/sound-touch-reactive-bottles-sensors</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Sep 22, 2025
		<h1>
			What smart tech can make bottles respond to sound or touch?
		</h1>
		<p>
			Smart tech that makes bottles respond to sound or touch—touch sensors, IMU motion, mic/beat and BLE—plus why OLED labels look premium in clubs.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>OLED vs LED in Wearables: Which Is Better for Night Visibility?</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/oled-vs-led-wearables-night-visibility</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Sep 17, 2025
		<h1>
			OLED vs LED in Wearables: Which Is Better for Night Visibility?
		</h1>
		<p>
			OLED vs LED in wearables: night-visibility verdict—OLED for presence, LED for alerts, reflective for compliance, plus layouts, tests, and standards.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>OLED Fashion: What It Is, How It Feels, and Why Wearing Light Changes the Way We’re Seen</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/what-is-oled-fashion</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Sep 15, 2025
		<h1>
			OLED Fashion: What It Is, How It Feels, and Why Wearing Light Changes the Way We’re Seen
		</h1>
		<p>
			OLED fashion is clothing and accessories that integrate organic light-emitting diode panels. Unlike point-like LEDs, OLEDs are ultra-thin, flexible, and printable area lights, so garments can glow softly, show logos or animations, and switch modes for day-to-night visibility, artistic expression, and interactive storytelling.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>OLED vs LED vs LCD: What’s the Difference? (2025 Guide)</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/oled-vs-led-vs-lcd-difference-2025</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Sep 9, 2025
		<h1>
			OLED vs LED vs LCD: What’s the Difference? (2025 Guide)
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover the key differences between OLED, LED, and LCD in this 2025 guide. Learn how OLED works, why it outperforms LED/LCD, and how printed OLED is transforming displays, packaging, and safety wearables.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What Is Interactive Packaging?</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/post-what-is-interactive-packaging-guide-</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Sep 4, 2025
		<h1>
			What Is Interactive Packaging?
		</h1>
		<p>
			Interactive packaging combines design and tech—like illuminated boxes and light-up cards—to create engaging, memorable brand experiences.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Do Light-Up Bottles in Bars Actually Work?</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/how-do-light-up-bottles-in-bars-actually-work</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Sep 3, 2025
		<h1>
			How Do Light-Up Bottles in Bars Actually Work?
		</h1>
		<p>
			How light-up bottles work in bars—glorifiers vs. luminous bottles vs. printed OLED labels—plus the tech, examples, and how to pilot your own.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What packaging ideas make bar drink bottles stand out?</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/post-packaging-ideas-bar-drink-bottles</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Sep 1, 2025
		<h1>
			What packaging ideas make bar drink bottles stand out?
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover packaging ideas that make bar drink bottles stand out—light-up OLED labels, bold shapes, textures, QR/AR, and eco-friendly designs.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What Is OLED? Definition, Technology &amp; the Future of Printed OLEDs (2025 Guide)</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/oled</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Aug 29, 2025
		<h1>
			What Is OLED? Definition, Technology & the Future of Printed OLEDs (2025 Guide)
		</h1>
		<p>
			OLED (Organic Light-Emitting Diode) is a thin, energy-efficient light source made of organic semiconductor layers that emit light when electricity passes through. Unlike LEDs, OLEDs need no backlight, enabling ultra-thin, flexible, and printable surfaces used in smartphones, TVs, wearables, safety gear, medical devices, and smart packaging.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>High Visibility Wearables: Protecting Kids, Runners, and Everyday Commuters with OLED Technology</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/high-visibility-wearables</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Aug 22, 2025
		<h1>
			High Visibility Wearables: Protecting Kids, Runners, and Everyday Commuters with OLED Technology
		</h1>
		<p>
			High visibility wearables are clothing and accessories that make people more visible in low light. They use reflective strips, LEDs, or OLED panels to actively emit light. This improves safety for workers, runners, cyclists, and children, reducing accident risks on roads and in dark environments.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What Is an OLED Manufacturer? Applications, Innovations, and Future Trends</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/oled-manufacturer-definition-applications-safety-smart-packaging</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Aug 21, 2025
		<h1>
			What Is an OLED Manufacturer? Applications, Innovations, and Future Trends
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover what an OLED manufacturer is, how OLEDs are transforming safety wearables, smart packaging, and medical devices, and why this technology is shaping the future of innovation beyond displays.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Safety Wearables with OLEDs: The Next Generation of Workplace Protection</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/safety-wearables-oled-vests</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Aug 19, 2025
		<h1>
			Safety Wearables with OLEDs: The Next Generation of Workplace Protection
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover how OLED safety wearables and LED vests improve workplace visibility and prevent accidents. Learn why OLED vests outperform traditional hi-vis gear in complete darkness.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>OLED Manufacturer: Definition, Industry Leaders &amp; Printed OLED Innovation (2025)</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/blog-oled-manufacturer-definition-printed-oled-innovation-2025-</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Aug 18, 2025
		<h1>
			OLED Manufacturer: Definition, Industry Leaders & Printed OLED Innovation (2025)
		</h1>
		<p>
			An OLED manufacturer makes organic light panels for displays and lighting. See 2025’s top players and how Inuru’s printed OLED tech cuts costs and waste.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What Are the Latest Packaging Trends? A 2025 Guide</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/packaging-trends-2025-guide</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Aug 14, 2025
		<h1>
			What Are the Latest Packaging Trends? A 2025 Guide
		</h1>
		<p>
			Explore the top packaging trends of 2025: eco-friendly materials, smart features, emotional design, and OLED-powered branding for interactive, sustainable experiences.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How to create eye-catching bottle packaging for bar marketing?</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/eye-catching-bottle-packaging-bar-marketing-</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Aug 13, 2025
		<h1>
			How to create eye-catching bottle packaging for bar marketing?
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover how to create eye-catching bottle packaging for bar marketing using OLED tech, behavioral psychology, and multisensory branding. Boost visibility and customer engagement in nightlife settings.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Do Light-Up Labels Enhance Brand Presence?</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/oled-light-up-labels-benefits-bars-events-</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Aug 12, 2025
		<h1>
			How Do Light-Up Labels Enhance Brand Presence?
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover how light-up OLED labels enhance brand presence in bars, clubs, and events—boosting visibility, engagement, and customer interaction through smart packaging.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What Are the Latest Innovations in Safety Wearables or Illuminated Garments?</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/latest-innovations-safety-wearables-illuminated-garments</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Aug 12, 2025
		<h1>
			What Are the Latest Innovations in Safety Wearables or Illuminated Garments?
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover the latest innovations in safety wearables and illuminated garments, including printed OLEDs, new EU safety standards, and data on how active lighting prevents accidents in low-visibility environments.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Can We Integrate Lighting into Automotive Interiors in a Flexible or Thin Format?</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/blog-flexible-thin-automotive-interior-lighting</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jul 28, 2025
		<h1>
			How Can We Integrate Lighting into Automotive Interiors in a Flexible or Thin Format?
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover how OLED technology enables flexible, ultra-thin lighting in automotive interiors—enhancing design, interaction, and energy efficiency.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How to Make Packaging More Interactive with OLED Technology</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/interactive-packaging-oled-technology</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jul 24, 2025
		<h1>
			How to Make Packaging More Interactive with OLED Technology
		</h1>
		<p>
			Discover how interactive packaging using OLED technology turns ordinary products into unforgettable experiences. Learn how brands like Coca-Cola and Cattier engage consumers through light-up labels and smart packaging innovation.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What Is Metaverse Fashion?</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/what-is-metaverse-fashion</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jul 18, 2025
		<h1>
			What Is Metaverse Fashion?
		</h1>
		<p>
			Metaverse fashion is a trend where digital clothing and accessories are designed for virtual spaces like gaming platforms, social media, and the metaverse. Today, that style is blending with physical fashion creating “phygital” garments that light up, interact, and even protect.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Inuru manifesto</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/inuru-manifesto</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		May 16, 2024
		<h1>
			Inuru manifesto
		</h1>
		<p>
			How Inuru fosters a world where humanity lives in balance with nature through the power of technology.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How to turn your product into an experience: Case Study on Coca-Cola X Star Wars &quot;Galactic bottles&quot; lit with Inuru OLED</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/how-to-turn-your-product-into-an-experience-case-study-on-coca-cola-x-star-wars-galactic-bottles-lit-with-inuru-oled</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Apr 30, 2024
		<h1>
			How to turn your product into an experience: Case Study on Coca-Cola X Star Wars "Galactic bottles" lit with Inuru OLED
		</h1>
		<p>
			In this post series we would like to shed light on how to turn your product into an experience, by including light and animation with into your products to make them ready to the new era of consumers.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How to Use Interactive Labels with OLED Technology in Marketing Campaigns Effectively</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/how-to-use-interactive-labels-with-oled-technology-in-marketing-campaigns-effectively</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Mar 21, 2024
		<h1>
			How to Use Interactive Labels with OLED Technology in Marketing Campaigns Effectively
		</h1>
		<p>
			Light is all about visibility and the structure that follows it. Despite living in a digital, data driven world, we still seem to live in the dark, when it comes down to creating a successful marketing or branding campaign. In the dynamic and ever-changing world of marketing, customers are inundated with various types of content—primarily on social media, television, and even in real life—the challenge lies in crafting a successful and attention-grabbing marketing campaign, in a world that has seen it all on TikTok. In the past, we have been working with the world’s best brands and their marketing geniuses, that all utilized our technology to create captivating events and strategically position products in new channels. Reviewing these campaigns today we can see a clear structure on what is successful and not. Today, we want to share this knowledge with you on how to make run a successful in the new era of digitization and Gen-Z coming into the market. In this article, we will analyze the successful marketing campaigns mentioned earlier. We’ll examine the factors that contributed to their success and explore areas where improvements could have been made. Let’s delve deeper into this topic.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Digital Fashion and the Metaverse Change the Clothes We Will Wear</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/how-digital-fashion-and-the-metaverse-change-the-clothes-we-will-wear</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jan 17, 2024
		<h1>
			How Digital Fashion and the Metaverse Change the Clothes We Will Wear
		</h1>
		<p>
			This article elaborates the hype behind digital fashion and how the today consumers digital experience will influence the design of fashion in the future. This article is for fashion designers and manufacturers who want to shape clothing and fashion of tomorrow.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Future of Board Games: A Journey from OLED Dreams to Reality</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/the-future-of-board-games-a-journey-from-oled-dreams-to-reality</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Dec 21, 2023
		<h1>
			The Future of Board Games: A Journey from OLED Dreams to Reality
		</h1>
		<p>
			Revolutionizing Board Games with OLED: From Fantasy to Reality – Discover how Inuru's OLED technology is transforming traditional board games into immersive, interactive experiences, starting with 'Streaks' by Buffalo Games.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Inuru makes OLEDs affordable</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/low-cost-oleds-for-low-cost-oled-labels-and-mass-market-adoption</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Oct 4, 2023
		<h1>
			How Inuru makes OLEDs affordable
		</h1>
		<p>
			How we make OLEDs affordable to bring OLED labels to mass market applications.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How Organic Lighting Technology Make Everyday Objects Smart like Medical Packaging and Expiry Date Indications</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/how-organic-lighting-technology-make-everyday-objects-smart-like-medical-packaging-and-expiry-date-indications</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Sep 5, 2023
		<h1>
			How Organic Lighting Technology Make Everyday Objects Smart like Medical Packaging and Expiry Date Indications
		</h1>
		<p>
			This posts describes the use of organic lighting technologies (OLED) for medical applications.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>What it takes to make Smart Packaging become reality</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/what-it-takes-to-make-smart-packaging-become-reality</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Apr 3, 2023
		<h1>
			What it takes to make Smart Packaging become reality
		</h1>
		<p>
			For 30 years, smart packaging has been an idea that has failed to achieve larger market adoption and has generally been underwhelming despite various companies' attempts. Inuru's latest generation of luminous labels have been launched with CATTIER's brand reboot for Glamour, impressing even one of the oldest Champagne houses in the world. Our labels have all the necessary characteristics for market-ready solutions, and we discuss our key deliverables for smart packaging.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The plan behind Inuru</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/post/the-plan-behind-inuru</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jun 10, 2022
		<h1>
			The plan behind Inuru
		</h1>
		<p>
			Why we have founded Inuru. The reason why we have invested 10 years to develop printed light.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Inuru Joins Global Goals Network to Support Sustainable Innovation</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/inuru-joins-global-goals-network-to-support-sustainable-innovation</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Nov 18, 2025
		<h1>
			Inuru Joins Global Goals Network to Support Sustainable Innovation
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru announces its new membership in the Berlin-based Global Goals network, an association dedicated to advancing the UN Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) and promoting the city's bid to host Expo 2035.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Inuru Wins the 2025 Polnisch-Deutscher Wirtschaftspreis</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/inuru-wins-polnisch-deutscher-wirtschaftspreis-2025</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Nov 6, 2025
		<h1>
			Inuru Wins the 2025 Polnisch-Deutscher Wirtschaftspreis
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru received the 2025 Polnisch-Deutscher Wirtschaftspreis from the Deutsch-Polnische Industrie- und Handelskammer (AHK Polen) for bringing OLED light technology back to Europe and strengthening European innovation.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>OLEDCON 2025: INURU Launches First Global Developer Conference for OLED in Everyday Products</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/oledcon-2025-inuru-oled-developer-conference-berlin</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jun 20, 2025
		<h1>
			OLEDCON 2025: INURU Launches First Global Developer Conference for OLED in Everyday Products
		</h1>
		<p>
			INURU announces OLEDCON 2025, the first global developer conference focused on OLED technology in packaging, clothing, and everyday products. Held on June 24th at NIO House in Berlin and supported by Berlin Partner, the event will feature a world premiere of INURU's printed display, visionary talks from global leaders in design and innovation, and hands-on OLED design workshops.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>&quot;Light Is the New Black&quot;: Program Announced for WORLD OLED DEVELOPERS CONFERENCE on 24th June in Berlin</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/light-is-the-new-black-oledcon</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jun 3, 2025
		<h1>
			"Light Is the New Black": Program Announced for WORLD OLED DEVELOPERS CONFERENCE on 24th June in Berlin
		</h1>
		<p>
			Experience visionary designs by Clara Daguin and try on real OLED-embedded clothing. From haute couture to smart workwear—light is the new black in wearable tech.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>First World OLED Developers Conference Announced</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/first-world-oled-developers-conference</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		May 20, 2025
		<h1>
			First World OLED Developers Conference Announced
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru is organizing its first-ever World OLED Developers Conference, bringing together designers, engineers, and creators to explore recent advancements in OLED technology. The event will highlight Inuru’s novel OLED manufacturing method, enabling cost-effective production of OLED lighting and displays in any shape or color. It also focuses on integrating OLEDs into various products, including packaging, textiles, and automotive parts. Attendees will participate in workshops, view demonstrations, and engage in shaping the roadmap from OLED illumination to complex display systems.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>We print displays-Inuru Prints Active Matrix OLED Display</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/we-print-displays-inuru-prints-active-matrix-oled-display</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		May 6, 2025
		<h1>
			We print displays-Inuru Prints Active Matrix OLED Display
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru, a leading European OLED display manufacturer, has achieved a major breakthrough by successfully printing OLED displays in three separate colors using its current-generation technology. Based in Berlin/Wildau, Germany, Inuru has confirmed its compatibility with active matrix backplanes—the standard for modern high-resolution screens—paving the way for affordable, flexible displays in packaging, wearables, and smart appliances. This milestone positions Inuru among the most innovative display manufacturers in Europe, offering printed OLED solutions beyond traditional TV and smartphone applications.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Engelbert Strauss Introduces Backpack with Inuru OLED Technology</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/engelbert-strauss-introduces-backpack-with-inuru-oled-technology</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Oct 11, 2024
		<h1>
			Engelbert Strauss Introduces Backpack with Inuru OLED Technology
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru's OLED Technology Adopted in Clothing and Workwear as Engelbert Strauss Introduces Backpack with Inuru OLED Technology
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Coca-Cola Introduces Light-Up Packaging using OLED from Dragon Factory in Partnership with Marvel and Rappi</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/coca-cola-introduces-light-up-packaging-using-oled-from-dragon-factory-in-partnership-with-marvel-and-rappi</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jul 22, 2024
		<h1>
			Coca-Cola Introduces Light-Up Packaging using OLED from Dragon Factory in Partnership with Marvel and Rappi
		</h1>
		<p>
			Coca-Cola Unveils Limited-Edition Thor Beverage with Inuru’s OLED Technology in Exclusive Collaboration with Marvel and Rappi
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Inuru Opens New Customer Experience Department in Warsaw</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/inuru-opens-new-customer-experience-department-in-warsaw</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Jul 7, 2024
		<h1>
			Inuru Opens New Customer Experience Department in Warsaw
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru's new Warsaw location to enhance customer interaction and accelerate OLED innovation with dedicated design and production units.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Caviar Lianozoff uses Inuru OLED labels for luxury branding</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/caviar-lianozoff-uses-inuru-oled-labels-for-luxury-branding</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Apr 10, 2024
		<h1>
			Caviar Lianozoff uses Inuru OLED labels for luxury branding
		</h1>
		<p>
			Caviar Lianozoff unveils Lumière, integrating Inuru OLED labels for a luxury branding and premium products experience.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Coca Cola Company explores Inuru OLED labels</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/the-coca-cola-company-explores-inuru-oled-labels</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Dec 21, 2018
		<h1>
			The Coca Cola Company explores Inuru OLED labels
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru releases world's first OLED label with The-Coca-Cola-Company.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Inuru launches low-cost OLED mass production at Dragon Factory Berlin-Brandeburg</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/inuru-launches-oled-mass-production-near-berlin</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Mar 11, 2024
		<h1>
			Inuru launches low-cost OLED mass production at Dragon Factory Berlin-Brandeburg
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru launches low cost OLED mass production.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Inuru Announces Opening of Revolutionary Dragon Factory: A New Era in OLED Technology</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/inuru-announces-opening-of-revolutionary-dragon-factory-a-new-era-in-oled-technology</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Feb 1, 2024
		<h1>
			Inuru Announces Opening of Revolutionary Dragon Factory: A New Era in OLED Technology
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru, a pioneer in OLED technology, proudly announces the grand opening of the Dragon Factory, the world’s first facility dedicated to the low-cost production of printed OLED lighting and displays.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Buffalo Games and Inuru release the First Game Board with OLED Lighting  &apos;Streaks&apos;,</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/buffalo-games-and-inuru-announce-revolutionary-collaboration-introducing-streaks-the-first-game-board-with-oled-lighting</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Dec 5, 2023
		<h1>
			Buffalo Games and Inuru release the First Game Board with OLED Lighting  'Streaks',
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru expands into Toy industry with first OLED board-game.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Displate and Inuru Announce Partnership to Bring Unique User Experience through OLED Technology</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/displate-and-inuru-announce-partnership-for-animated-luminous-posters</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Apr 7, 2023
		<h1>
			Displate and Inuru Announce Partnership to Bring Unique User Experience through OLED Technology
		</h1>
		<p>
			Displate and Inuru have partnered to create a new product category called LUMINO.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Cattier Introduces Luminous Champagne Labels with Inuru.</title>
			<link>https://www.inuru.com/news/cattier-uses-luminous-labels-for-champagne</link>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<html>
	<head>
	</head>
	<body>
		Oct 1, 2023
		<h1>
			Cattier Introduces Luminous Champagne Labels with Inuru.
		</h1>
		<p>
			Inuru teams up with Packhelp to deliver high quality marketing solutions.
		</p>
	</body>
</html>]]></content:encoded>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
